I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Somehow graduating from
state university, I made my way...
...into a businessman's city.
I get kicked around by my superior.
But I yearn to be like that someday,
in order to remain sane in this place.
This is the city of winter, where I lived.
However, all that seems so far away.
All I see before me is the azure of
the China Sea, stirring winds, and...
Okay, Mr. Japanese, I'll ask you again.
The package you got from Asahi
Industries headquarters in Tokyo.
The one you're in charge of until you
hand it over to the chief in Borneo.
This is it, right?
Yeah. But what I wanna know is...
That's all. That's everything
we needed to ask you.
Dutch, this is a pain in the ass.
Shoot him in the knees. Then
he'll start singing like a bird.
There's no need. That one disk is
more than enough for the compensation.
Compensation, you say.
Dutch. Hey, Dutch.
Are you through yet?
There's someone heading
straight for us from Subic Bay.
It's probably...
...a patrol boat
from the Filipino Navy.
Don't panic, Benny-boy. Everything's
taken care of. Start the engines.
Okay, gentlemen!
We're gonna disperse and
then you'll be free to go.
But the deal's off if anyone
decides to come after us.
What you see there is
a torpedo launcher.
If you don't wanna be blown
out of the water...
...then stay still for the next half hour.
After that, you're free to do as you wish.
We're saved.
What are you getting so relaxed over?
You're coming with us. You damn fool.
You're joking. You're joking, right?
Shut up and walk.
You're joking, right?!
Japan is drifting farther away.
Black Lagoon to Balalaika.
Can you hear me?
Just fine, Dutch. What about the catch?
I've got it, of course.
I love jobs that get done properly, Dutch.
The trade-off goes as planned.
Yes, as promised.
Connect me to Tokyo.
How about an explanation, Investigation
Division Manager Kageyama?
Regarding the case we
have been informed about.
Let me explain the situation
to you further.
Today at 4 pm, the Bougainvillea
Trade Company contacted us...
...regarding negotiations for the
disk stolen from the Melanesia.
What is this company?
They're the Russian Mafia.
The front for the group
that aims to take...
...top position after displacing the
Chinese Mafia from Southeast Asia.
What are they specifically after? Money?
Most likely the route to Southeast Asia
where the barter is going to take place.
They wish to take part in some of
our more unsavory trade routes.
Blackmail.
It's shameful, having something
to be blackmailed about.
But they do not seem to know
what's really on the disk.
If they ever find out, it will lead to...
...the worst scandal
in Asahi Industries' history.
Indeed.
We just received a report from Jakarta.
According to a local Chinese merchant...
...the Russian Mafia has
yet to receive the disk.
The disk is still in the hands of the
pirates that attacked the Melanesia.
This is our chance. We cannot
trust the word of the Mafia.
We must get the disk
before it reaches them.
Before it reaches them? But how?
I understand. The board will leave
this matter in your hands, Kageyama.
Choosing what action to take
will also be your responsibility.
Revy, what do you plan on
doing with this hostage? Well?
You don't get it. You
just don't get it, Dutch.
Think about it! We get twenty grand
for this job! Only twenty grand!
What's wrong with collecting a
bonus by asking for a ransom?
You're being simpleminded.
You wanna get killed, Benny?!
Not really.
So, who's gonna negotiate
with them? You?
Do you have their phone number?
What about a bank account
to receive the ransom?
Fine then!
We'll just kill his ass
and throw him overboard!
Stop it!
You idiot! Stop damaging the ship!
Shut up!
Dutch. Dutch, I get it.
Get what?
I get your point, so let me go.
Okay, Revy. Let's play it cool.
I'm alive. I don't know
why, but somehow I'm alive.
All right, all right. Let's
go on deck for a smoke.
What's gonna happen to me?
We'll contact your company
somehow and set up a trade.
A ransom, huh? This'll go
on my permanent record.
But we have our own priorities. Getting
the disk to our client comes first.
So there's a client.
We're just delivery boys.
We brush up against the law
from time to time so we can eat.
But that's business.
I guess this is what they
call the Stockholm Syndrome.
At this moment I feel like
this big guy next to me...
...is the only one I can
trust in the whole world.
What's your name?
Okajima. Rokuro Okajima.
What's the name of that employee?
It's Okajima, Director. Rokuro Okajima.
It is entirely the fault
of my managerial skills.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I was only informed recently, sir.
And because there was no
other employee...
...we could trust with vital information...
...we lost valuable time in
confirming our sources.
That's enough. Kageyama,
what are your thoughts?
Our company is in a crisis.
We cannot accept any more delays.
The E.O. Company, with whom we've
made a confidential contract...
...has already sent their professionals.
Well, it was your responsibility.
But I do feel bad for this
employee. What's his name?
It's Okajima, Director. Rokuro Okajima.
Let's go, Rock.
Rock?
I think he means you.
So let's go.
Go where?
Some place where we can have
a drink. Don't you wanna come?
But I thought I was a hostage.
We're leaving.
Wait! I'm coming too!
But where on Earth am I?
I just don't get it.
Why is there a pistol on every table?
Is this the so-called "bar at the end of
the world" you see in cowboy westerns?
Good analogy.
This place was started by Southern
Vietnamese soldiers...
...who survived the war.
But they started taking
in fugitive soldiers too...
...and before we knew it,
the place went to hell.
Hookers, junkies, mercenaries, hitmen...
Irredeemable criminals.
Make you uncomfortable?
Japanese pubs...
I love those unguarded smiles.
Places like this...
Shut up or I'll throw you
out onto the beach. Damn it.
I don't like confrontations.
Your expression says it all.
Benny, I'm gonna make a call.
Sure.
He's a bit unusual, the big guy.
All I know about him after
being around him for two years...
...is that he's tough,
intelligent and eccentric.
Don't even try to understand him.
Thanks. You seem different from
the others. Where were you before?
A university in Florida.
I was fooling around and pissed
off the Mafia and the FBI. Then...
I saved his ass before he was
thrown overboard in a suitcase.
Stop the worthless storytelling.
You're not old enough to be
reminiscing about the past.
One for you, one for me.
We came all the way here for a drink.
Let's talk about something a
little more hip, mister Japanese.
Why, this is...
Beer's no different than piss.
No matter how much you drink
you can't get buzzed.
If you're a man, you'll take rum. But...
...if you don't have the balls to
take on a challenge from a woman...
I won't force you.
But I'll make you wear a skirt,
and a pretty ribbon...
...and take you to a dance party.
I hate chugging down drinks! However...
We're forced to drink at university
parties and company socials.
Don't underestimate
Japanese businessmen!
You...
Hey, bartender!
Bring all the Bacardi you've got!
Well, well... I thought you
didn't like confrontations.
Is that so? That can't be good. Go on.
I didn't trust Asahi Industries' response.
So I left out bait, and a Chinese rat
jumped right in. I'm talking to him now.
Who's on the move?
One moment.
Tell me your owner's
name, loud and clear.
Sh-Shingian! Shingian's Wan Taikei!
Wan Taikei sent an assassin to get you!
He's sent an assassin to Roanapur!
Hear that?
Yeah. Not good.
Tell me the number and affiliation
of those soldiers.
Speak loud. Hurry, we're busy.
G-Guys from Extra Order, a
mercenary contracting agency!
I don't know how many there are!
The E.O. Company scouts
experienced war junkies.
Rotten luck.
You said it.
Let's get started.
Okay, guys. It's party time.
Give anyone trying to
escape extra assholes!
Make sure there are only
corpses when we're done.
Revy! If they're your
friends, you deal with them!
I don't know them.
Wow, you've bulletproofed the bar.
It can handle up to a. 50 caliber.
Revy!
I'm alive.
Benny!
Miraculously, I'm alive.
What about Rock?!
Dead! People are dead!
I went through all the trouble
of graduating university...
...and got into a good
company! This isn't fair!
Don't cry, fool. You've gotta enjoy
life, or you'll let it waste away.
Revy! Show them why you're
known as "Two-Hands"!
Check the place out. I heard voices.
I hate survivors!
What a great line.
Got 'em, Dutch!
Don't come back here,
Revy! You're a nuisance!
How many times have
you destroyed my bar?!
You owe me for all this!
Or else I'll weld your asshole shut
and make you a new one in your head!
Got it. Dutch!
She's...smiling.
Sorry, but at this rate, trading
you is no longer an option.
Then what's gonna happen to me?!
Well, you weren't really in our plans.
How about we just part ways here?
That's not fair! I'm gonna die!
Take me with you!
Fine then. Just don't drag
us down. Revy! We're leaving!
Gotcha!
Get in!
Take this, you war junkies!
Hey Dutch.
Bao was so pissed, he
looked like a steaming pot.
He says that unless we pay him
back he's gonna weld our assholes.
Scary. I think I'm gonna cry.
What the hell is this? Is this a movie?
Don't be stupid. This is a lot
more entertaining than Hollywood.
Captain! Sixteen dead, eight
wounded! I'm sorry, sir.
We thought of them as no more than
punks and underestimated them.
Storm, they're not just any
group of punks.
They're a troop that can stage a
decent killing fest against us.
In Liberia, all we had to shoot
at were old men and brats.
Too slow, and no fight left in them.
But these guys are full of vigor. I've
been waiting for something like this.
If we maintain this speed, we'll
be at the Belawan port by daybreak.
We'll meet Balalaika there. So, Rock...
Benny is getting in touch with
your company as we speak.
So there is a way to
do stuff like this!
If negotiations don't go well, we're gonna
have to leave you in Malaya. Sorry.
There are bandits all around there,
but I'm sure you'll be okay for a while.
Okay?
What do you mean?!
You bring me all this
way just to let me die?!
What is this, after dragging
me all over the place?
The least you could do is
take me someplace safe!
Don't push your luck.
First you cry, then you wanna
use us as a taxi? All right then.
Why don't I show you what
color your brain is?!
No...
We're connected. We're using an
Assault Dial so the line's secure.
Rock, it's your boss, Mr. Kageyama.
Department chief! Okajima
speaking. I'm very sorry.
Now, regarding the loss of the disk...
Right. Don't worry about that
anymore. That disk no longer exists.
I don't understand.
Given the situation, I'll tell
you, and only you...
...the truth. Don't tell anyone else.
It's hard to explain...
...but to hedge against a drop in
business, our board of directors...
...agreed to help a war-torn country with
the development of nuclear weapons.
That disk contained the plans.
It's nothing but trouble for management.
Nukes in this day and age... It
makes me doubt their judgment.
Eventually I'll be...
...at the top and then I can do
something about this.
But in the meantime, this
cannot be made public, Okajima.
For the sake of the 50,000
employees of Asahi Industries...
...I want you to disappear
into the South China Sea.
You'll be promoted two ranks, to
assistant manager.
We won't treat you badly.
I'll also ask for the president and
everyone under him...
...to attend your funeral.
The professional ruffians
should be there shortly.
Is it loaded?
Fully equipped, Captain.
Whatever you fire, whether it's
rockets or the machine guns...
...all the more to add to the invoice.
The Japanese are
such generous spenders.
Okay, let's go!
They sure ditched you easily.
Though I do sympathize.
There goes the ransom and bonus.
But is it really enough to make
you throw up?
Leave me alone.
Revy. Are you on the deck?
Yeah.
There's something coming
straight at us over the ocean...
...but it's not a boat. It's too fast.
It's way too fast. At 3 hours 5
minutes. Can you see anything?
It's a low-altitude assault gun-ship!
Damn it! An assault helicopter?!
We have visual!
I don't need to see them. I can
smell them. I know it's them.
Damn them. They're gonna
use that thing to kill me.
Rock! Grab onto this!
A gun?! Don't make me hold this!
Though it won't be more
than a comfort to you.
He's coming. He's on our ass.
This isn't good! In fact, this is really bad!
He's firing at us!
I know it isn't good, Dutch!
Hit it! Shoot it down!
Shut up! You try it, dumb-ass Rock!
I hope you realize that you're
hiding under a torpedo launcher!
Make sure you don't get blown up!
Rock, you bastard!
I've had it with you guys!
I'm getting outta here!
You impotent son of a
bitch! You running away?!
Stop it! Why should I suffer like this?!
All right. Let's just sit back
and observe from up here.
But Captain, right now, we have an
opportunity to turn them into mincemeat.
You don't get it, do you?
They're in my trap, from
their heads to their tails.
Don't you wanna laugh at them while
they cry, howl, and piss themselves?
Damn it! How dare you do
whatever you want with me!
Every one of you! Even
the Department Head!
Why the hell should I suffer like this?!
Next Episode
I'm already dead. You told me so.