I have a big gun
I took it from my lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Weapon . . . I have it all
I see now.
But we can't lend out Rock.
We are off the case.
But... why?
Your chief is going to take on Uncle Sam,
an ally of every nation, with her bare hands.
You have to admit that's insane.
Precisely.
She is trying to face off against the United States itself.
Then that's all the more reason...
She is my family!
I am the only one in this world who can save her.
That is exactly why...
What an annoying brat.
Did you fly half way around
the world just to cry like that?
Then it's your chance! Cry a whole bucket.
Who knows? A comic book hero
might come and save you.
Why, you...
Fabiola, it's all right.
You are absolutely correct.
I cannot ask any more of you.
We will continue the search on our own.
You...
have really changed.
You have become a full-fledged man.
The only people I could depend upon, my father and Roberta, are now gone.
That is the only reason.
I see.
Is that all you have to say, Rock?
Abandoning these two kids in a town like this would make even me feel uneasy.
If at all possible,
I'd rather they left the rest to us and
returned to their mansion in Venezuela.
Then...
That's not like you, Mr. Chang.
There's not an ounce of truth to what you just said.
Was it too corny for you, Dutch?
The maid will confront the US Army sooner or later.
That wouldn't do any good for the town, nor for me.
That's none of our concern.
Keeping the order here is your job.
Cut it, Dutch.
Here's a man who's familiar with this town, got many business connections,
and harmful to no one, holding a neutral position that won't complicate the situation.
Wouldn't you say their pick was spot on, Rock?
Why don't you help out those kids?
This town, as a whole, hopes
that the maid leaves before things get complicated.
Everything will resolve itself
if I take them and catch up with the maid before she clashes with the US Army.
Is that your request, Mr. Chang?
It's a simple game plan, isn't it?
Please give me a little time. I'd like to think it through properly.
Listen. If you can't get his assistance, leave this town as soon as possible.
Listen to what us adults tell you.
Rock.
At this rate, that kid's hair will turn white before he's 20.
Give it a good thought.
See you then, Young Master.
"It's just like looking for a missing cat."
"I can squeeze it into my workday."
Did you think I'd let you off with a line like that, Rock?
The problem comes after you stick
your nose into it looking for the cat.
As soon as you open the closet, this cat will bite your torso clean off.
Let me tell you one thing.
And no arguing, 'coz I'm the boss.
Listen. If the maid and the US Army clash before you get there,
you get out of there right away, at all costs!
Another simple game plan, is it?
Will he take it up?
That's the way he works.
He's a rare type of person in this town.
He's so easily moved.
A number of syndicates dwell here in Roanapur:
The Hong Kong Triads,
Hotel Moscow,
La Cosa Nostra,
The Colombian Cartel,
and numerous others.
Once a port used during the Second World War to help accommodate the Japanese navy,
Roanapur has since transformed into one great port of drug smugglers,
and to this day remains a labyrinth.
And you're telling me to help those kids out of this?
Let's think. Think my anxiety away.
Believe in myself.
Where can I intervene?
There's the fountainhead of drugs...
and here's the mouth, this very town.
Damn it!
How far do I have to go 'til you're satisfied?
No, let's first...
eliminate.
This matter does not involve the Italians.
But this situation was partly triggered by the South American Cartel.
Gustavo said they have forces coming from home.
The FARC will conduct the pursuit of the maid firsthand.
Then ensues a three-way struggle among the maid, the US Army, and the FARC.
And the street fighting...
Real military forces?
I have a question.
Is it about your retirement savings?
You're persistent.
Well, yeah.
Balalaika once said she was indebted to you big time.
What does that mean?
You're going off on a strange tangent.
It could be relevant to the matter at hand.
So where should I begin?
From the very beginning.
It'll take a while.
Yep, got it, Dutch.
That's what she meant.
Bye. And with that...
another piece of the puzzle is put in place.
There are quite a few left.
Are these really all the syndicates here in Roanapur?
And that makes a Full House.
I win all $230!
Damn you.
"God loves a cheerful giver."
You're usually out of good cards when you keep raising it like mad.
So what's up between you and Rock this time, Two Hand?
You always follow him like a d—
It's way too dangerous.
The problem is the people that maid's after.
What did they do?
They blew her master all the way up to the moon.
Are they terrorist bombers?
It's Uncle Sam and his merry soldiers.
The United States...
Army?
Yeah.
Boiling hot with rage, the maid's going to make meat patties out of those soldiers.
So why are those soldiers coming over to this shithouse place?
No idea.
In the first place, there's no way I could follow his every whim.
I thought through everything I possibly could.
This time, I'll definitely...
Hello.
Oh, it's you. What's the matter?
Fabiola! Have you seen Mr. Rock?
That makes it the fourth time you've asked about him since sunrise.
I see. You are right.
Let me take another walk around the town.
I may pick up some clues.
Hey.
Sorry we're late.
What's the matter?
Was it that unexpected?
Well,
I should not be saying this,
but I thought you would not come.
It's always fun to solve puzzles, you see.
It's just as I told you over the phone.
The maid came here and left. I have no idea where she is.
Well, so, how did this happen?
It's not just me.
The brothel upstairs is also closed because of that kid over there.
So I'm just cooling off with the girls like this.
Is this really your doing?
No, that is...
I asked you to settle things peacefully.
I am terribly sorry.
Bao.
Did you provide for the maid?
No.
I'm not obliged to tell you all that, you know.
Please, Bao.
Well...
Fine then.
But I have one condition.
If things go wrong, vouch that
I wasn't involved in any of this.
Sure thing.
Promise me in writing later too.
It's a matter of life and death.
So what happened last night?
Yes, last night...
What did you just say?
"Please direct me to a store with every item necessary for a war."
Hell no. You've got to be jok—
Does this seem like a drunkard's joke?
While I was calling everywhere to connect her, she was chewing on antidepressant pills
as if she were stuffing herself
with popcorn at a movie theater.
So you directed her to Praiyachat, Torch, and backstreet doctor Doc Hartland.
The doctor's for her to get the pills, right?
She never told me the petty details, nor do I want to know.
Thanks for everything. I'll return this favor sometime.
By the way, you're not with Two Hands today.
Did you guys have a fight or something?
No, it's just...
Señor Rock!
Y-Yes? What is it?
We spent the entire day walking around just to have every place you mentioned practically refuse us at the door.
You owe me an explanation.
Well, that's...
That is not what we talked about at all!
Don't get too angry. Of course it isn't.
Your chief is a celebrity here.
A girl dressed up just like the infamous maid,
and a boy that looks more high-class than anyone this town has seen before.
You can't expect anyone to answer us when we're walking around with the two of you.
In any case, we need to get things moving.
I will investigate by myself tomorrow.
Fabiola, unfortunately...
We cannot do it by ourselves.
However...
You...
don't seem intimidated by this town at all.
I was raised in a similar place full of idiots and trash.
So it's familiar, to a degree.
She is from the barrios of Caracas.
The barrios?
That's what it's known as.
It is a slum where people do not even have an address.
You can see the area shine like the Milky Way at night in Caracas.
The reason these poor slum houses are so bright is...
because everyone steals their electricity from the electric company.
That's very resilient.
You put it too nicely.
But you are my family now.
Well, there are eleven people in my real family,
and my parents will be less burdened with me apprenticing here.
Then did you train your gun and leg skills there, too?
Leg skills?
Watch your words.
What do you mean by leg skills?
It is capoeira, Young Master.
That is...
There were guys in the neighborhood in training, so I learned it by imitating them.
I know capoeira. It's a great combat sport!
Show me sometime, Fabiola!
I-If you do not mind a self-taught style, sometime.
As I previously stated, my hometown was not a decent place, so I had to learn self defense.
A careless gunshot can kill people, but I have control over this.
So I thought it would be a skill worth training.
Well said. I think so, too.
I largely approve of that mindset, but whether it would work here is a different story.
Though I'm not used to giving people advice,
you do have to aim at the enemy's weakest point and pull the trigger without hesitation when necessary.
But that is a bad temptation.
Even Roberta could not resist it.
I do not want Fabiola to tread the same path.
Well then, you two will be staying at
Mr. Chang's yacht house from now on.
It's a hideout with security guards and a pool.
We'll be off after we drive you there.
Y-Yeah.
We'll be waiting in the car, so finish your dishes first.
I never knew you could say such things.
Well, I wouldn't want to see the kids die.
But this is about all I can do for them.
Just how tough must a person be to cope with the deaths around him?
That's why I don't get too involved.
Rock, can you endure it?
I see, I see.
NSA and CIA are fighting over their territory.
We, the CIA, are bound to know of any mission that has been approved by the AIC.
Depending on their moves, we may have to utilize the intelligence network.
The trigger of this situation,
Venezuelan political activity intervention plan 114,
has also been planned and carried out without our involvement.
They most likely intend to broaden their control over espionage missions,
taking advantage of the CIA's shift to a focus on economic information warfare.
This is incredibly displeasing.
Maintaining a big family...
sure gets difficult.
Well, all right. Let us keep close track of any Americans lurking in the town then.
You are a valuable client after all.
We appreciate it. My boss should get back to you regarding payment and other details.
For starters, people should be gathering for a conference at Golden Swinging Nightclub,
one hosted by the Triads.
I don't know about the Young Master, but the maid was really excited about Mr. Chang's yacht house.
Yeah.
Why are you so down?
It's the Mafia.
Where are they headed to?
To a liaison group to discuss
the case we're also involved in.
Oh, I see.
Reality is moving closer to my predictions from last night.
So this evening's meeting will determine her future, huh?
No, it won't be determined just yet.
Not yet?
There's not that much time left for both ourselves and the Young Master.
Remember what Dutch said?
Watch out for critical turning points.
The turning point is still ahead of us.
The turning point at the clash lies even further in the future.
Hey, Balalaika. Is today your birthday? It's quite a party.
Are we here today just for your bad Italian jokes?
I'll just leave then.
What?
Calm down, Tomazzo. She's a country bumpkin who doesn't know how to socialize.
Hey, Amigo, sorry to cut your playtime short, but we'd like to get things rolling here.
Precisely.
By now, Chang should be telling everyone about the maid and the enemy she's after.
But those who don't understand how serious the situation is
will make fun of it.
Got it. The solution is extremely simple, Mister.
Host a party for them to make up.
Pop open some champagne, get a huge cake and bring in some dancer girls with big boobs.
Since when did Sicily get into the comedy business?
Shut up, you sloppy Ivan!
Let's go on.
Behind the terrorist bombing that killed the maid's master, there are military personnel on active service.
Chang talks about the identity of Roberta's enemy.
That is sure to grab Balalaika's attention,
for the Russian Mafia under her were once part of the Soviet Air Forces,
soldiers trained to match the US Army in the Third World War.
But the Colombian Cartel will react completely differently.
To keep our relations with the FARC intact, we need to bring them the maid's head pickled in salt.
We will be hunting that maid down!
It's unexpected, but you seem to have some guts.
However, our enemy is not the maid but rather her enemy.
The Yankees' goal is simple: an anti-drug campaign.
We must strike before they have their way with this town.
Thirty-five years have passed since this decaying port became the metropolis of vice.
The only reason why this outlaw Roanapur
never appeared in the headlines of the New York
evening news, nor became the talk of the town was...
because we, the rulers of this town, shared the same vision.
But this town is frail and feeble at best.
If we were to allow outsiders to intervene even once,
who will remain standing in the ring at the end?
Nobody will be there, ladies and gentlemen.
Neither you nor I, not even the ring itself.
However, even if they recognize the impending crisis, they won't be able to locate Roberta immediately.
Where is she?
I only have so much information to guide me.
Yet I can't even follow up with it. Damn it!
El Señor conoce mis debilidades.
The Lord seest my weaknesses.
Porgue nada es posible, sin la gracia de Dios,
For naught is possible without the grace of God,
te pido Señor que los consignes como consideres necesario.
let Your countenance abound those who answer unto You.
Permite a este discipulo evitar los pecados enviados,
Commit not sin upon thy fellow disciple,
y llevar a cabo, con rectitud, de los designios de tus palabras...
but proclaim His virtues throughout the world.
Y dotame de fuerza para que pueda acoger y sobreponerme...
Heavenly Father, bestow upon us the strength to endure...
You'd be better off not taking that drug.
A los retos que me impones por tu divina gracia.
the mortal challenges imposed on us, with Your divine grace.
You are already overdosing.
Are you not going to return to that orchid-blooming estate?
There's a kid awaiting your return there.
Is what you're pursuing really revenge? Or are you...
Both Master and Young Master deserved heavenly blessing.
I alone will take responsibility for my sin! Yet...
You cannot compensate for your past no matter how much you repent...
even if you were to drive yourself to ruin.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Whoa, wait, don't shoot! It's me, Leroy!
What's up with you? All I did was get clothes as you ordered, but you—
What about the wanted poster?
Everything's taken care of.
Now it's just a matter of money.
Who in the world...
were you talking with just now?
So what do you want me to do?
We are pressured for time. I'd like to catch up with the maid immediately.
Rock, you're not trying to make amends for being unable to save that schoolgirl's
yakuza boss dad back in your country, are you?
No...
Then, when you stuck up to Sis to save her,
something inside you must have emerged from the depths of desperation.
Am I wrong?
A hobby you say?
Yes, it's my hobby, just like yours.
As you said, it's your dangerous personal hobby.
How do I justify keeping up with that? Tell me.
You always support me in my moments of gravest danger. I do thank you for that.
Thank me, eh?
What do you think?
See, I need to perform a ritual before joining the gamble.
Under what pretext should I follow you and your nonsense?
I'm...
I'm done with just waiting and seeing.
When we were in my country, you said you were a gun.
If you are the gun, I am the bullet.
But I'm nothing more than
a piece of lead right now.
Had I never come to this town, I would have died as a mere piece of lead.
But I did come.
The gunpowder is sitting there waiting to explode.
The only thing that can light it...
is the gun.
"Light My Fire", is it?
Don't you know? It's a number by The Doors.
Rock, what kind of a bullet are you?
A Full Metal Jacket?
A Hollow Point?
Or a Glaser Safety Slug?
No. You are the unpredictable silver bullet.
It has enough power to obliterate an invincible monster.
It's a pricey but invincible bullet.
Yet...
it's over if you miss the timing. The monster will devour you.
I'm out of water.
Rock, there's a vending machine downstairs. Get some for me.
Hey, use baht. It'll break if you use nickels.
Got it.
Really, no fair.
Oh, Revy. I'll bring the water right up.
Old man Praiyachat should be around at this time of day.
We have to return to the ship by evening.
Let's get it over with, Rock.
Young Master?
Are you asleep?
Good.
Someone's having a good time.
You happy, kid?
There are pools in Venezuela, too.
It is only that I've personally never swum in a pool.
S-So I just... For a little...
Still, you didn't have to sneak out to swim.
My sincerest apologies.
Hey, Young Master.
How can she ask you for time off when you're
desperately looking for that goddamn glasses bitch?
She's that devoted to you.
You carry a whole family upon your shoulders, and you still can't see that?
Do not talk so rudely to Young Master!
Stop it!
We are going to visit the same places today.
Is the old man here? This is Rebecca from the Lagoon Company.
Oh, it's you, Revy. How're your Cutlasses doing?
They're doing great. But that's not what I came here for today.
Hmph, another one of these...
So do you want me to choose one for her, then?
That means she was here...
a woman like this one, only taller and with glasses, right?
Bao referred her to here,
so I gave her an offer though I never saw her before.
What did she ask for? Was it a gun?
No, actually,
she already had her own gun.
It was a rather antique flintlock rifle of 18th century Spain.
Young Master.
I know, Fabiola.
That's the gun that used to be displayed in our banquet hall.
She asked me to refurbish it so she could use it.
It was in an okay condition so it was no problem.
She still needs gunpowder like cordite or black powder though.
Is that why she asked for Blaster Torch?
Wait, Revy.
Your grip is crooked.
The butt of a gun is for knocking brains out, no?
Idiot, this is a one-of-a-kind!
Torch! Hey, Blaster Torch!
Y-You! I thought I blocked your death wave with the aluminum foil,
and now you're here to do it yourself!
Fine then. I'll take you on! Fucker!
What is this?
Just play along with him.
Hey, hey, calm down.
She might be a space alien, but she's a good alien!
I don't trust you!
You are as punctual as always, Mr. Chang.
It's one of my virtues. Let's get down to business.
Oh, so it wasn't a woman?
It was the guy who works as a broker, a tip-off, or something.
Who was it again?
Don't do drugs in the middle of a conversation, idiot!
Who was the tip-off?
Oh, damn it! I can't remember.
It should jump out at me after a shot of heroin. Can I, Revy?
Stop fucking around!
The unit who infiltrated the town, formed to carry out advanced political selections under the NSA,
is the 9th operation unit of Pentagon's
Special Operations Command, SOCOM,
and although listed as the 56th Engineer
Construction Battalion in the command hierarchy,
at the JCS, it is known as...
"The Gray Fox Command Group."
So it's the foxes being chased by the bloodhound maid.
Their main mission is to capture General Shue Yan, the most powerful warlord under Khun Sa in the Golden Triangle
and call him to the Supreme Court of the United States.
It should bring about utter grief to the Triads,
for the Triads' heroin purification facility will be useless without the General's opium fields.
When is the date?
Late this month; the assault team consists of eighteen men.
They disguised their way in as backpackers traveling together, and are currently on standby at the motels here.
Their locations:
Squad Alpha is at Tokaina Hotel;
Squad Bravo is at Blue Moon Motel;
Squad Charlie is at Lansup Inn.
Major Caxton, the commander, is with Squad Alpha.
That's enough, Agent.
We are not done.
Tell me your countermeasure.
I don't think there's that much trust between us.
You're just sucking up to the government at best.
Don't think you can boss us around.
You are terribly mistaken. Let me give you a piece of advice.
We do not suck up to the government.
Think of the United States as a gigantic hydra with countless heads.
You may have the power to bring
individuals and companies to their knees,
but we have enough power to annihilate entire countries.
Indeed, we are the single strongest being in the entire world.
And so...
don't you look down on my company...
punk.
Let me see.
Roy, Roy...
Lero...
Wait, that's right!
It's Richie Leroy!
Richie Leroy is directly involved with the maid!
That's the puzzle's final missing piece!
Let's go!
NEXT EPISODE
Young Master is waiting in the garden for me to return with the heads of the conniving foxes.
Young Master will greet me with a smile, and everything will be back to normal.